Guide to the TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
- Poker According to Maverick [BC: Ad for Kaiser Aluminum, with Logo] by J. Hoyt Cummings Dell First Edition B142 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 25)
- Poker According to Maverick [BC: Ad for Kaiser Aluminum, without Logo] by J. Hoyt Cummings Dell First Edition B142 ca. 1959 (2nd: 1960) (Box 25)
- Maya #1: The Forbidden City by Norman Daniels Berkley F1538 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 25)
- Medical Center by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Popular Library 01336 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 25)
- Medical Story by Abby Mann Signet W6785 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 26)
- Medical Story #2: Kill Me, Please by William Johnston Signet W6802 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 26)
- The Men From Shiloh #1: Lone Trail for the Virginian by Dean Owen [Dudley Dean McGaughy] Lancer 74775 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 26)
- Men Into Space by Murray Leinster [Will F. Jenkins] Berkley G461 ca. 1960 91st) (Box 26)
- Miami Undercover by Evan Lee Heyman Popular Library G554 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 26)
- Miami Vice #1: The Florida Burn by Stephen Grave [David J. Schow] Avon 89930 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 26)
- Miami Vice #2: The Vengeance Game by Stephen Grave [David J. Schow] Avon 89931 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 26)
- Miami Vice #2: The Vengeance Game by Stephen Grave [David J. Schow] Star ca. 1985 (Variant Cover) (Box 26)
- Miami Magic by Caroline Latham Zebra 8217-1800 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 26)
- Don Johnson by David Hershkovits St. Martin's Press 90165 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 26)
- Don Johnson: An Unauthorized Biography by Suzanne Munshower Signet AE4345 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 26)
- The Making of Miami Vice by Trish Janeshutz and Rob MacGregor Ballantine 33669 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 26)
- Michael Shayne: Murder Takes No Holiday by Brett Halliday [Robert Terrall] Dell D379 ca. 1960 (1st: 1961) (Box 26)
- Michael Shayne: The Corpse Came Calling by Brett Halliday [Davis Dresser] Dell D401 ca. 1942 (1st new Dell: 1961) (Box 26)
- Michael Shayne's Long Chance by Brett Halliday [Davis Dresser] Dell D416 ca. 1944 (1st new Dell: 1961) (Box 26)
- Michael Shayne: Death Has Three Lives by Brett Halliday [Davis Dresser] Dell D423 ca. 1955 (1st new Dell: 1961) (Box 26)
- Michael Shayne: Dolls Are Deadly by Brett Halliday [Ryerson Johnson] Dell D424 ca. 1960 (1st new Dell: 1961) (Box 26)
- Michael Shayne: Stranger in the Town by Brett Halliday [Davis Dresser] Dell D425 ca. 1955 (1st new Dell: 1961) (Box 26)
- Michael Shayne: The Homicidal Virgin by Brett Halliday [Davis Dresser] Dell D437 ca. 1960 (1st new Dell: 1961) (Box 26)
- Michael Shayne: Killers From the Keys by Brett Halliday [Ryerson Johnson] Dell 4476 ca. 1961 (1st new Dell: 1962) (Box 26)
- The Michaels in Africa: I Married a Hunter by Marjorie Michael Pyramid PR14 ca. 1957 (1st: 1958) (Box 26)
- The Secret World of Roy Williams by Roy Williams Bantam 1697 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 26)
- Mission Impossible by John Tiger [Walter Wager] Popular Library 60-8042 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 26)
- Mission Impossible #2: Code Name: Judas by Max Walker Popular Library 60-2261 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 26)
- Mission Impossible #3: Code Name: Rapier by Max Walker Popular Library 60-2325 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 26)
- Mission Impossible #4: Code Name: Little Ivan by John Tiger [Walter Wager] Popular Library 60-2464 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 26)
- The Original Mr. Ed by Walter Brooks Bantam J2530 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 26)
- Mr. Lucky by Albert Conroy [Marvin H. Albert] Dell First Edition B165 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 26)
- The Mod Squad #1: The Greek God Affair by Richard Deming Pyramid X-1888 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 26)
- The Mod Squad: The Greek God Affair by Richard Deming Pyramid X2319 ca. 1968 (2nd: 1970) (Variant Cover) (Box 26)
- The Mod Squad #2: A Groovy Way to Die by Richard Deming Pyramid X-1908 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 26)
- The Mod Squad #3: The Sock-it-to-Em Murders by Richard Deming Pyramid X-1922 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 27)
- The Mod Squad #3: The Sock-it-to-Em Murders by Richard Deming Pyramid ca. 1968 (Alternate Copy) (Box 27)
- The Mod Squad #4: Spy-In by Richard Deming Pyramid X-1986 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 27)
- The Mod Squad #5: The Hit by Richard Deming Pyramid X-2214 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 27)
- Mod Squad: Home is Where the Quick Is by William Johnston Pinnacle P027-N ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 27)
- The Monkees by Gene Fawcette and Howard Liss Popular Library 50-8026 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 27)
- The Monkees Go Mod by Patrick O'Connor Popular Library 60-8046 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 27)
- Love Letters to the Monkees by Bill Adler, ed. Popular Library 60-8049 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 27)
- The Monkees Go Ape by Bill Adler, ed. Popular Library 60-8069 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 27)
- Mork & Mindy by Ralph Church Pocket 82729 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 27)
- Mork & Mindy 2: The Incredible Shrinking Mork by Robin S. Wagner Pocket 83677 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 27)
- Mork & Mindy: A Video Novel by Richard A. Anobile Pocket 82754 ca. 1978 (1st: 1979) (Box 27)
- The Robin Williams Scrapbook by Mary Ellen Moore Ace Tempo Star 73200 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 27)
- Robin Williams ["The Robin Williams Scrapbook" abridged] by Mary Ellen Moore Grosset & Dunlap ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 27)
- Mork & Mindy: Code Puzzles From Ork by D.J. Arneson Cinnamon House 15879 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 27)
- Mork & Mindy Puzzlers by Mary Beth Lewis Cinnamon House 15880 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 27)
- The Most Deadly Game #1: The Corpse in the Castle by Ed Friend [Richard Wormser] Lancer 73200 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 27)
- The Most Deadly Game #2: The One-Armed Murder by Richard Gallagher Lancer 73216 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 27)
- The Munsters by Morton Cooper Avon G1237 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 27)
- Murder, She Wrote: The Murder of Sherlock Holmes by James Anderson Avon 89702 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 27)
- Murder, She Wrote #2: Horray for Homicide by James Anderson Avon 89937 ca. 1985 (1st) (Box 27)
- Murder, She Wrote #3: Lovers and Other Killers by James Anderson Avon 89938 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 27)
- My Friend Tony by William Johnston Lancer 73-838 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 27)
- The Naked City by Charles Einstein Dell First Edition A180 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 27)
- Nakia by Lee Hays Popular Library 08325 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 27)
- Name of the Game: Loa Angeles: A.D. 2017 by Philip Wylie Popular Library 00272 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 27)
- Nancy by Jack Pearl Pyramid T2339 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 27)
- Nanny and the Professor by William Johnston Lancer 73876 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 27)
- The New Avengers #1: House of Cards by Peter Cave Berkley 03993 ca. 1976 (1st: 1978) (Box 27)
- The New Avengers #2: The Eagle's Nest by John Carter Berkley 03994 ca. 1976 (1st: 1978) (Box 27)
- The New Avengers #3: To Catch a Rat by Walter Harris Berkley 03995 ca. 1976 (1st: 1978) (Box 27)
- The New Avengers #3: To Catch a Rat by Walter Harris Futura ca. 1976 (Box 27)
- The New Avengers #4: Fighting Men by Justin Cartright Futura ca. 1977 (Box 28)
- The New Avengers #5: Last of the Cybernauts by Peter Cave Futura ca. 1977 (Box 28)
- The New Avengers #6: Hostage by Peter Cave Futura ca. 1977 (Box 28)
- The New Breed by Lee Costigan [Hank Searls] Gold Medal s1186 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 28)
- The New People: They Came From the Sea by Alex Steele [William Johnston] Tempo 05308 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 28)
- "The Newlywed Game" Cookbook by Jody Cameron Malis Pocket 75652 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 28)
- Night Gallery by Rod Serling Bantam S7160 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 28)
- Night Gallery 2 by Rod Serling Bantam S7203 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Night Stalker by Jeff Rice Pocket 78343 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Night Strangler by Jeff Rice Pocket 78352 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Nurses by William Johnston Bantam F2497 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 28)
- One Life to Live #1/#2 [combined]: Moonlight Obsessions, Books One and Two by Gwendolynn Arden Pioneer 400 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 28)
- One Step Beyond: The World Grabbers by Paul W. Fairman Monarch 471 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Outcasts by Steve Frazee Popular Library 60-2345 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Outsider by Lou Cameron Popular Library 60-2373 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Paper Chase by John Jay Osborn, Jr. Popular library 04357 ca. 1971 (1st: 1978) (Box 28)
- The Paper Chase by John Jay Osborn, Jr. Warner 31141 ca. 1971 (1st: 1983) (Variant Cover) (Box 28)
- Paper Dolls by Susan Beth Pfeffer Dell 96777 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 28)
- Paper Dolls by Susan Beth Pfeffer Dell 96777 ca. 1984 (2nd) (Box 28)
- Paper Moon [orig. title "Addis Pray"] by Joe Davis Brown Signet W6409 ca. 1971 (15th: 1974) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family by Michael Avallone Curtis 05003 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family #2: The Haunted Hall by Michael Avallone Curtis 05004 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family #3: Keith, the Hero by Michael Avallone Curtis 05005 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family #4: The ghost of Graveyard Hill by Paul W. Fairman Curtis 06147 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family #5: Terror by Night by Vic Crume Curtis 06148 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family #6: Keith Partridge, Master Spy by Vance Stanton [Michael Avallone] Curtis 06150 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family #7: The Walking Fingers by Vance Stanton [Michael Avallone] Curtis 06162 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family #8: The Treasure of Ghost Mountain by Paul W. Fairman Curtis 06164 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family #9: The Fat and Skinny Murder Mystery by Vance Stanton [Michael Avallone] Curtis 06180 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family #10: Marked for Terror by Vic Crume Curtis 06182 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 28)
- The Partridge Family #11: Who's That laughing in the Grave? by Vance Stanton [Michael Avallone] Curtis 06184 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 29)
- The Partridge Family #12: The Phantom of the Rock Concert by Lee Hays Curtis 06189 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 29)
- The Partridge Family #13: The Mystery of the Man Millionairess by Edward Fenton Curtis 06186 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 29)
- The Partridge Family #14: Thirteen at Killer Gorge by Vic Crume Curtis 06190 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 29)
- The Partridge Family #15: The Disappearing Professor by Lee Hays Curtis 06191 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 29)
- The Partridge Family #16: The Stolen Necklace by Lee Hays Curtis 07321 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 29)
- The Partridge Family #17: Love Comes to Keith Partridge by Michael Avallone Curtis 07335 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 29)
- The David Cassidy Story by Carol Deck Curtis 06154 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 29)
- David, David, David by James Gregory Curtis 06167 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 29)
- The Partridge Family Cookbook by Sylvia Resnick Curtis 09219 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 29)
- Young Mr. Cassidy by James A. Hudson Scholastic Book Services TK2070 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 29)
- Susan Dey's Secrets On Boys, Beauty & Popularity [formerly "For Girls Only"] by Susan Dey as told to Rochelle Reed Tiger Beat LAU 1 ca. 1972 (2nd) (Box 29)
- The Patty Duke Show: Patty goes to Washington by Frances Spatz Leighton Ace F-278 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 29)
- People Are Funny by Art Linkletter Cardinal C-384 ca. 1947,60 (1st: 1960) (Box 29)
- Perry Mason: The Case of the Gilded Lady by Eric Stanley Gardner Cardinal C-337 ca. 1956 (1st: 1959) (Box 29)
- Perry Mason: The Case of the Dubious Bridegroom by Eric Stanley Gardner Cardinal C-376 ca. 1949 (1st: 1959) (Box 29)
- Perry Mason: The Case of the Screaming Woman by Eric Stanley Gardner Cardinal C-377 ca. 1957 (1st: 1959) (Box 29)
- Perry Mason: The Case of the Perjured Parrot by Eric Stanley Gardner Cardinal C-379 ca. 1939 (1st: 1959) (Box 29)
- Perry Mason: The Case of the Hesitant Hostess by Eric Stanley Gardner Cardinal C-381 ca. 1953 (1st: 1959) (Box 29)
- Perry Mason: The Case of the Fan-Dancer's Horse by Eric Stanley Gardner Pocket 886 ca. 1947 (4th: 1957) (Box 29)
- Perry Mason: The Case of the Daring Decoy by Eric Stanley Gardner Pocket 6001 ca. 1957 (1st: 1960) (Box 29)
- Perry Mason: The Case of the Lonely Heiress by Eric Stanley Gardner Pocket 6027 ca. 1948 (4th: 1960) (Box 29)
- Perry Mason: The Case of the Calendar Girl by Eric Stanley Gardner Pocket 6040 ca. 1958 (1st: 1960) (Box 29)
- Perry Mason: The Case of the Fiery Fingers by Eric Stanley Gardner Pocket 6044 ca. 1951 (6th: 1960) (Box 29)
- The Persuaders! Book One: The Heart-Shaped Birthmark by Frederick E. Smith Ballantine 02630 ca. 1971 (1st: 1972) (Box 29)
- The Persuaders! Book Two: Five Miles to Midnight by Frederick E. Smith Ballantine 02633 ca. 1971 (1st: 1972) (Box 29)
- Peter Gunn by Henry Kane Dell First Edition B155 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 29)
- Peyton Place by Grace Metalious Pocket 75087 ca. 1956 (1st: 1965) (Box 29)
- Peyton Place by Grace Metalious Pocket 75087 ca. 1956 (13th: 1968) (Variant Cover) (Box 29)
- Again Peyton Place by Roger Fuller Pocket 75196 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 29)
- Carnival in Peyton Place by Roger Fuller Pocket 75250 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 29)
- Pleasures of Peyton Place by Roger Fuller Pocket 75267 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 29)
- Secrets of Peyton Place by Roger Fuller Pocket 75285 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 30)
- The Evils of Peyton Place by Roger Fuller Pocket 75334 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 30)
- Hero in Peyton Place by Roger Fuller Pocket 75367 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 30)
- The Temptations of Peyton Place by Roger Fuller Pocket 75423 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 30)
- Thrills of Peyton Place by Roger Fuller Pocket 75457 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 30)
- Nice Girl from Peyton Place by Roger Fuller Pocket 75470 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 30)
- The Girl From "Peyton Place" by George Metalious and June O'Shea Dell 2888 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 30)
- The Tight White Collar by Grace Metalious Pocket 77023 ca. 1960 (1st: 1968) (Box 30)
- No Adam in Eden Grace Metalious Pocket 75002 ca. 1963 (1st: 1964) (Box 30)
- Sergeant Bilko [mouth open version] by Nat Hiken Ballantine 229 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 30)
- Sergeant Bilko [mouth closed version] by Nat Hiken Ballantine 229 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 30)
- Sgt. Bilko Joke Book Ballantine 289K ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 30)
- Phylis Diller's Housekeeping Hints by Phylis Diller Crest R1082 ca. 1966 (1st: 1968) (Box 30)
- Phylis Diller's Housekeeping Hints by Phylis Diller Crest T2027 ca. 1966 (unsp: 1969) (Box 30)
- Phylis Diller's Marriage Manual by Phylis Diller Crest R1245 ca. 1967 (1st: 1969) (Box 30)
- Planet of the Apes #1: Man the Fugitive by George Alec Effinger Award AN1373 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 30)
- Planet of the Apes #2: Escape to Tomorrow by George Alec Effinger Award AN1407 ca. 1974,75 (1st: 1975) (Box 30)
- Planet of the Apes #3: Journey Into Terror by George Alec Effinger Award AN1436 ca. 1974,75 (1st: 1975) (Box 30)
- Planet of the Apes #4: Lord of the Apes by George Alec Effinger Award AN1488 ca. 1974,76 (1st: 1976) (Box 30)
- The Comedian and Other Stories by Ernest Lehman Signet 1446 ca. 1946+ (1st: 1957) (Box 30)
- No Time At All by Charles Einstein Dell D224 ca. 1957 (1st: 1958) (Box 30)
- Please Don't Eat the Daisies by Jean Kerr Crest d834 ca. 1953+ (unsp: 1965) (Box 30)
- Please Don't Eat the Daisies by Jean Kerr Crest d834 ca. 1953+ (13th: 1966) (Variant Cover) (Box 30)
- Police Woman #1: The Rape by Leslie Trevor Award AQ1438 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 30)
- Police Woman #2: Code 1013: Assassin by Leslie Trevor Award AQ1452 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 30)
- Police Woman #3: Death of a Call Girl by Leslie Trevor Award AQ1487 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 30)
- Primus by Bradford Street [Al Hine] Bantam S7262 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 30)
- Primus by Bradford Street [Al Hine] Bantam S7262 ca. 1971 (1st) (Special Edition) (Box 30)
- The Prisoner by Thomas M. Disch Ace 67900 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 30)
- The Prisoner #2: Number Two by David McDaniel Ace 67901 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 30)
- The Prisoner #3: A Day in the Life by Hank Stine Ace 67902 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 30)
- Prisoner Cell Block H by Murray Sinclair Pinnacle 41113 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 31)
- Private Eye #1 by T.N. Robb [Rob MacGregor] Ivy 0269 ca. 1988 (1st) (Box 31)
- Private Eye #2: Blue Movie by David Elliot [David Elliot Pedneau] Ivy 0270 ca. 1988 (1st) (Box 31)
- Private Eye #4: Nobody Dies in Chinatown by Max Lockhart [Doris R. Meredith] Ivy 0272 ca. 1988 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Quest Tapes by D.C. Fontana Ballantine 24236 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 31)
- Quincy, M.E. #2 by Thom Racina Ace 69946 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Rat Patrol by Norman Daniels Paperback Library 53-387 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Rat Patrol #2 in Desert Danger by David King Paperback Library 53-411 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Rat Patrol #3 in The Trojan Tank Affair by David King Paperback Library 53-477 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Rat Patrol #4 in Two-Faced Enemy by David King Paperback Library 53-566 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Rat Patrol #5 in Target for Tonight by David King Paperback Library 53-628 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Rat Patrol #6 in Desert Masquerade by David King Paperback Library 53-696 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 31)
- Rawhide by Frank C. Robertson Signet S1910 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 31)
- Rebel of Broken Wheel by Dean Owen [Dudley Dean McGaughy] Monarch 218 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Restless Gun by Will Hickok [C. William Harrison] Signet 1541 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 31)
- Trail of the Restless Gun by Will Hickok [C. William Harrison] Signet 1675 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 31)
- Return to the Planet of the Apes #1: Visions from Nowhere by William Arrow [William Rotsler] Ballantine 25122 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 31)
- Return to the Planet of the Apes #2: Escape form Terror Lagoon by William Arrow [Don Pfeil] Ballantine 25167 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 31)
- Return to the Planet of the Apes #3: Man, the Hunted Animal by William Arrow [William Rotsler] Ballantine 25211 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 31)
- All About "Rhoda" by Peggy Herz Scholastic Book Services TK3121 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 31)
- Ripley's Believe It or Not #32 Signet AE2213 ca. 1982 (1st) (Box 31)
- Roald Dahl's Tales of the Unexpected by Roald Dahl Vintage 74081 ca. 1948+ (1st: 1979) (Box 31)
- The Roaring 20's: Sing Out Sweet Homicide by John Roeburt Dell First Edition K105 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Rockford Files #1: The Unfortunate Replacement by Mike Jahn Popular Library 00318 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Rockford Files #2: The Deadliest Game by Mike Jahn Popular Library 00354 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 31)
- The Rookies by Claire Parker Bantam N7703 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 31)
- Room 222: What Ever Happened to Mavis Rooster? by William Johnston Tempo 05339 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 32)
- Room 222 #2: Monday Morning Father by William Johnston Tempo 05342 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 32)
- Room 222 #3: Love is a Three Letter Word by William Johnston Tempo 05358 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 32)
- Room 222 #4: Bomb in the Classroom by William Johnston Tempo 05372 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 32)
- Room 222 #4: Bomb in the Classroom by William Johnston Tempo 05591 ca. 1971 (Box 32)
- Room 222 #5: A Little Grass on the Side by William Johnston Tempo 05414 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 32)
- Room 222 #6: Have you heard about Kelly? by William Johnston Tempo 05594 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 32)
- S.W.A.T. #1: Crossfire! by Dennis Lynds Pocket 80241 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 32)
- The Saint Steps In by Leslie Charteris Fiction K101 ca. 1942,43 (1st: 1963) (Box 32)
- The Saint Sees it Through by Leslie Charteris Fiction K102 ca. 1946 (1st: 1963) (Box 32)
- The Saint Closes the Case by Leslie Charteris Fiction K103 ca. 1930 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- The Avenging Saint by Leslie Charteris Fiction K104 ca. 1930,31 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- The Saint's Getaway by Leslie Charteris Fiction K105 ca. 1932,33 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- The Saint in New York by Leslie Charteris Fiction K106 ca. 1934,35 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- Enter the Saint by Leslie Charteris Fiction K107 ca. 1930,31 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- The Saint Meets His Match by Leslie Charteris Fiction K108 ca. 1941 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- Featuring the Saint by Leslie Charteris Fiction K109 ca. 1931 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- Alias the Saint by Leslie Charteris Fiction K110 ca. 1931 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- The Saint Overboard by Leslie Charteris Fiction K111 ca. 1935,36 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- The Saint - The Brighter Buccaneer by Leslie Charteris Fiction K112 ca. 1933 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- The Saint vs The Scotland Yard by Leslie Charteris Fiction K113 ca. 1932 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- The Saint and Mr. Teal by Leslie Charteris Fiction K114 ca. 1933 (1st: 1964) (Box 32)
- The Saint in the Sun by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-238 ca. 1963 (1st: 1966) (Box 32)
- The Saint Goes West by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-246 ca. 1942 (1st: 1966) (Box 32)
- Saint Errant by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-247 ca. 1933+ (1st: 1966) (Box 32)
- The Saint on the Spanish Main by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-252 ca. 1949+ (1st: 1966) (Box 32)
- Trust the Saint by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-253 ca. 1962 (1st: 1966) (Box 32)
- The Saint Around the World by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-260 ca. 1954+ (1st: 1966) (Box 32)
- The Saint Intervenes by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-262 ca. 1934 (1st: 1966) (Box 32)
- The Saint Goes On by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-265 ca. 1934,35 (1st: 1966) (Box 32)
- Call for the Saint by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-273 ca. 1947,48 (1st: 1967) (Box 33)
- The Saint in Europe by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-294 ca. 1936,53 (1st: 1967) (Box 33)
- The Saint to the Rescue by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-307 ca. 1956+ (1st: 1968) (Box 33)
- Senor Saint by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-315 ca. 1953+ (1st: 1968) (Box 33)
- Thanks to the Saint by Leslie Charteris Macfadden 60-365 ca. 1956,57 (1st: 1968) (Box 33)
- Vendetta For The Saint by Leslie Charteris Pocket 50212 ca. 1963,64 (1st: 1966) (Box 33)
- The Saint Abroad by Leslie Charteris Curtis 07137 ca. 1969 (1st: 1971) (Box 33)
- The Saint in New York by Leslie Charteris Curtis 07184 ca. 1934,35 (1st: 1971) (Box 33)
- The Saint Overboard by Leslie Charteris Curtis 07185 ca. 1935,36 (1st: 1971) (Box 33)
- The Saint and the Fiction Makers by Leslie Charteris Curtis 07199 ca. 1968 (1st: 1971) (Box 33)
- The Saint on TV by Leslie Charteris Curtis 07200 ca. 1967,68 (1st: 1971) (Box 33)
- The Saint Sees it Through by Leslie Charteris Curtis 07209 ca. 1946 (1st: 1971) (Box 33)
- The Saint in Miami by Leslie Charteris Curtis 07210 ca. 1940 (1st: 1971) (Box 33)
- Sam Benedict: Cast the First Stone by Elsie Lee Lancer 70-035 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 33)
- The Sandy Duncan Story by Rochelle Reed Pyramid 02934 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 33)
- Sanford and Son by Alan Riefe and Dick Harrington Curtis 09222 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 33)
- Backstage at Saturday Night Live! by Michael McKenzie Scholastic Book Services 30919 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 33)
- Search by Robert Weverka Bantam S7706 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 33)
- Search: Moonrock by Robert Weverka Bantam N8306 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 33)
- Search for Tomorrow [old logo version] by Faith Baldwin popular Library 60-8017 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 33)
- Search for Tomorrow [new logo version] by Faith Baldwin popular Library 60-2163 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 33)
- Secret Agent: Departure Deferred by W. Howard Baker Macfadden 50-275 ca. 1965 (1st: 1966) (Box 33)
- Secret Agent: Hell For Tomorrow by Peter Leslie Macfadden 50-280 ca. 1965 (1st: 1966) (Box 33)
- Secret Agent: Storm Over Rockall by W. Howard Baker Macfadden 50-284 ca. 1965 (1st: 1966) (Box 33)
- Secret Agent: Storm Over Rockall by W. Howard Baker World Distributors 794 ca. 1965 (Box 33)
- Secret Agent: No Way Out by Wilfred McNeily Macfadden 50-320 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 33)
- Secret Agent: No Way Out by Wilfred McNeily World Distributors 804 ca. 1966 (Box 33)
- Secret Agent: The Exterminator by W.A. Ballinger [W. Howard Baker] Macfadden 50-342 ca. 1966 (1st: 1967) (Box 33)
- The Secret Storm: The Unseen by Joan Hughes Pocket 75444 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 33)
- Serpico by Peter Mass Bantam 10265 ca. 1973 (23rd: 1976) (Box 33)
- The Double Take by Roy Huggins Pocket 2524 ca. 1946 (2nd: 1959) (Box 33)
- 77 Sunset Strip by Roy Huggins Dell First Edition A176 ca. 1958 (1st: 1959) (Box 33)
- Shaft Among the Jews by Ernest Tidyman Bantam N7621 ca. 1972 (1st: 1973) (Box 34)
- Shaft Has a Ball by Ernest Tidyman Bantam N7699 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 34)
- Shaft's Carnival of Killers by Ernest Tidyman Bantam N8494 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 34)